NIGHTCLUBBING Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong 1970-2009 (Bulk 1975-1980) MSS 305
Fales Library and Special Collections
NIGHTCLUBBING Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong
Bulk, 1975-1980
1970-2009
MSS 305
Fales Library and Special Collections
16.0 cubic feet
NIGHTCLUBBING was a weekly cable television show produced by video artists Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong. The NIGHTCLUBBING Archive is a collection of videorecordings featuring live footage filmed between 1975 and 1980 that captures the burgeoning punk scene in nightclubs around New York City.
Biographical Note
Pat Ivers attended New York University's Tisch School of the Arts before working at Manhattan Cable TV's Public Access Department. She began documenting New York City's downtown nightclub scene in the 1970s, working with Nam Juin Paik and other video artists, as well as the Metropolis Video collective and Emily Armstrong. In the 1980s Ivers was instrumental in the creation of the Corporate and Cable Communications Program (now The Media Arts and Technology Department) at the Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) of The City University of New York (CUNY). She began working for ABC Sports in the 1990s and is currently a Producer/Editor at WPIX.
Emily Armstrong scheduled, produced, and promoted television programs as a coordinator in Manhattan Cable TV's Public Access Department in the 1970s. Together with Pat Ivers, a fellow MCTV employee, Armstrong began documenting New York City's downtown nightclub scene to present on the weekly cable television show NIGHTCLUBBING. Armstrong designed and ran the Professional Video Training Program (PROVIT), which retrained thousands of NYC trade union media professionals in new digital technologies. She also worked as a New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA) Video Artist-In-Residence in the public school system.
Sources:
Go Nightclubbing
Historical Note
NIGHTCLUBBING, a weekly cable television show produced by video artists Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong, debuted in 1979. The show was comprised of live footage filmed between 1975 and 1980 by Ivers and Armstrong that captures the burgeoning punk scene in nightclubs around New York City, including CBGB, Mudd Club, and Danceteria. The recordings feature dynamic performances by Bad Brains, Ballistic Kisses, Max Blagg, Blondie, Bush Tetras, John Cale, Contortions, Cramps, Dead Boys, Dead Kennedys, DNA, Go Go's, The Heartbreakers with Richard Hell, Richard Hell and the Voidoids, Levi and the Rockats, The Lounge Lizards, Offs, Iggy Pop, Pylon, Strange Party, The Stilettos with Tish and Snooky, Suburbs, Suicide, Teenage Jesus and the Jerks, Talking Heads, and many others.
Sources:
Bedford+Bowery: Nightclubbing
Go Nightclubbing
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
Provenance
The Fales Library purchased the Nightclubbing Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong from Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong in 2010.
Arrangement
This arrangement retains the collection's original order. Titles of the videos derive from the titles provided by Ivers and Armstrong. The videos are arranged chronologically, then alphabetically, in the following series:
Series I: Performances
Series I contains live performances recorded by Ivers and Armstrong for the weekly cable television show NIGHTCLUBBING. The footage captures various artists and musicians performing in nightclubs around New York City between 1976 and 1980. This series also includes undated recordings as well as later recordings from 1997 and 2003.
Series II: Interviews
Series II contains video interviews with various musicians, performance artists, critics, and writers involved in the New York City punk scene. Many of the videos are undated. The dated interviews were all made in the 2000s except for one recording from 1977.
Series III: The Come-On's
The seven videos in Series III comprise two shoots and rough edits of The Come-On’s video installation project. The project allowed participants to select to view a tape of a performer, or “seducer,” in a photo booth. Each tape featured a musician or artist from the downtown scene who attempted to “seduce” the viewer.
Series IV: Narrative Tapes
The six videos in Series IV comprise narrative tapes, which functioned as the precursor to modern music videos. In each narrative tape, an artist’s performance is accompanied by thematically relevant stories, images, and video clips.
Series V: Video Lounge
The nineteen videos in Series V contain Video Lounge footage captured by Ivers and Armstrong. The artists created the Video Lounge format after being commissioned to design a video installation for the opening of the Danceteria nightclub in 1980. Video Lounge became a permanent feature at Danceteria but Ivers and Armstrong also included the format in the NIGHTCLUBBING television series, which showed video art, various video clips and footage, and musical performances.
Series VI: Nightclubbing
The sixteen videos in Series VI contain episodes of the NIGHTCLUBBING television series that was broadcast as a local television show in New York City and was also screened at late night viewings at the Anthology Film Archives. While the majority of these recordings are undated, the dated videos were made during 1975-1980.
Scope and Content
The NIGHTCLUBBING Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong is a collection of videorecordings produced by video artists Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong for the weekly cable television show NIGHTCLUBBING. The videos feature live footage filmed between 1975 and 1980 that captures the burgeoning punk scene in nightclubs around New York City. The videorecordings vary by type and include live performances captured for the television show; interviews with various musicians, performance artists, critics, and writers; a video installation project; narrative tapes; Video Lounge footage; and episodes of the NIGHTCLUBBING television series.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
The Peter Dougherty Collection
Downtown Flyers and Invitations
Richard Hell Papers
April Palmieri Papers
Amos Poe Papers
David Wojnarowicz Papers
Bad Brains (Musical group).; Blondie (Musical group).; Bush Tetras (Musical group).; Contortions (Musical group).; Cramps (Musical group).; Dead Boys (Musical group).; Dead Kennedys (Musical group).; DNA (Musical group).; Go Go's (Musical group).; Hell, Richard; Iggy, Pop, 1947-; Levi and the Rockats (Musical group).; Lindsay, Arto; Lounge Lizards (Musical group).; Lunch, Lydia; Offs (Musical group).; Pylon (Musical group).; Ramones (Musical group).; Suburbs (Musical group).; Suicide (Musical group).; Talking Heads (Musical group).; Teenage Jesus and the Jerks (Musical group).; White, James Chance, 1953-; Artists |z New York (State) |z New York.; Avant-garde (Music); Cable television; Cable television |x Access.; Downtown Collection.; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.) |v Fiction.; Music |z New York (State) |z New York |x Performance |x History.; Punk rock music.
- Series I: Performances
  Scope and Content
  Series I contains live performances recorded by Ivers and Armstrong for the weekly cable television show NIGHTCLUBBING. The footage captures various artists and musicians performing in nightclubs around New York City between 1976 and 1980. This series also includes undated recordings as well as later recordings from 1997 and 2003.
  - Sidewalk Café Interviews at Upper East Side NYC, 1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0146)
    Existence and Location of Copies note
    DVD access copy available.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Currently available.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    Black & White, Sound
    Duration: 33 minutes
    Original format: 1/2" open reel
  - Friends Forever at Bob Fass's Loft, Summer 1976 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0120)
    Color, Sound
    Duration: 26 minutes
  - Dead Boys at CBGB, October 1977 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0001)
    Duration: 53 minutes
    Original format: 3/4" Umatic
  - Dead Boys at CBGB, October 1977 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0002)
    Duration: 39 minutes
  - Foolish Virgins at Max's, October 1977 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0003)
    Color / Black & White, Sound
    Duration: 12 minutes
  - Foolish Virgins at Max's, October 1977 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0004)
    Duration: 22 minutes
    Original Format: 3/4" Umatic
  - Foolish Virgins at Max's, October 1977 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0005)
    Duration: 21 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit Edit at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0006)
    Duration: 57 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Cosmo Interview, Two Timers, Corpse Grinders at CBGBs, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0007)
  - Blitz Benefit - Dead Boys, Idols, Closing Ambience at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0014)
    Duration: 24 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Dead Boys with Divine and the Neon Women at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0012)
    Duration: 32 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Dead Boys with John Belushi and Jonathan Paley, Helen Wheels Band at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0008)
  - Blitz Benefit edit at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0016)
  - Blitz Benefit edit at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0017)
  - Blitz Benefit edit at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0018)
    Duration: 25 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Erasers (no audio), backstage ambience at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0015)
    Duration: 29 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Interviews with Cheetah, Norman, Mark Ross, Girls Room Ambience at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0009)
  - Blitz Benefit - Kathy Kurls, Dead Boys at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0011)
  - Blitz Benefit - Leggs McNeill and Tish, Criminals, Kathy Kurls at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0010)
  - Blitz Benefit - Sirius Trixon at CBGB, May 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0013)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, July 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0019)
    Duration: 8 minutes
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, July 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0020)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, July 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0021)
    Duration: 30 minutes
  - Helen Wheels at CBGB, September 23, 1978 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0066)
  - Dead Boys at Max's, March 1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0022)
  - Dead Boys at Max's, March 1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0023)
    Duration: 17 minutes
  - Dead Boys at Max's, March 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0024)
  - Dead Boys at Max's, March 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0025)
    Duration: 20 minutes
  - Cuban Heels at CBGB, April 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0127)
    Duration: 23 minutes
  - Desire at CBGB, April 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0026)
  - Desire at CBGB, April 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0027)
  - Stiletto Fads at CBGB, April 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0028)
  - Stiletto Fads at CBGB, April 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0029)
  - Ballistic Kisses at Danceteria, June 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0037)
    Duration: 34 minutes
  - Brainiacs at Mental Health Records, June 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0032)
  - Brainiacs at Mental Health Records, June 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0119)
    Alternate title: Brainiacs at Mental Health Records, June 1979 2/2
  - Dead Kennedys at Hurrah's, June 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0033)
  - Dead Kennedys at Hurrahs, June 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0121)
    Duration: 22 mimutes
    Alternate title: Dead Kennedys at Hurrahs, June 1979 2/2
  - Dils at Hurrah's, June 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0030)
  - Dils at Hurrah's, June 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0031)
  - Rock Against Racism - Crayola, Heat at Max's, June 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0034)
  - Rock Against Racism - Stiletto's at Max's, June 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0036)
  - Rock Against Racism - Unknown bands at Max's, June 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0035)
    Format: DVD
    Duration: 00:21:54
  - Voidoids at CBGB, August 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0038)
  - Voidoids at CBGB, August 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0039)
    Duration: 00:07:52
  - Casulties at Max's, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0051)
    Color/ Black & White, Sound
    Duration: 18 minutes
  - Destroy All Monsters at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0041)
  - Futants at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0050)
  - Heartbreakers at Max's, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0045)
  - Heartbreakers at Max's, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0046)
  - Heartbreakers at Max's, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0047)
  - James "Blood" Ulmer at Danceteria, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0053)
    Duration: 40 minutes
  - Lounge Lizards at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0048)
  - Lounge Lizards, Futants at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0049)
  - Only Ones at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0042)
  - Only Ones at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0043)
    Duration: 10 minutes
    Original fDVD access copy available.ormat: 3/4" Umatic
  - Only Ones at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0044)
  - Revelons at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0054)
    Alternate title: Revelons at CBGB, September 1979 1/2
  - Revelons at CBGB, September 1979 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0105)
    Alternate title: Revelons at CBGBs, September 1979 2/2
  - Senders at The 80's, September 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0052)
  - Levi / Rockats at CBGB, October 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0055)
    Alternate title: Levi/Rockats at CBGB, October 1979 1/3
  - Levi and the Rockats at CBGB, October 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0056)
    Alternate title: Levi and the Rockats at CBGBs, October 1979 2/3
  - Levi and the Rockats at CBGB, October 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0057)
    Black & White and Color, Sound
    Duration: 11 minutes
    Alternate title: Levi and the Rockats at CBGBs, October 1979 3/3
  - Sick Dick and the Volkswagons at Max's, November 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0126)
  - Wazmo Nariz at The 80's, November 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0058)
  - Bad Brains at CBGB, December 1979 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0107)
    Duration: 31 minutes
  - Iggy Pop at Hurrah's, December 1979 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0059)
    Alternate title: Iggy Pop at Hurrah's, December 1979 2/2
  - Iggy Pop at Hurrah's, December 1979 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0106)
    Duration: 1 hour 3 minutes
    Alternate title: Iggy Pop at Hurrah's, December 1979 1/2
  - Our Daughters Wedding at Danceteria, December 1979 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0060)
    Duration: 35 minutes
  - 3 Teens Kill 4 at Peppermint Lounge, 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0123)
    Duration: 15 minutes
  - Cheetah Chrome and the Casulaties at Max's, February 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0065)
  - Colors at CBGB, February 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0061)
    Alternate title: Colors at CBGB, February 1980 1/2
  - Colors at CBGB, February 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0062)
    Alternate title: Colors at CBGB, February 1980 2/2
  - Pin-ups at CBGB, February 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0101)
  - Student Teachers at CBGB, Feburary 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0063)
    Duration: 7 minutes
    Alternate title: Student Teachers at CBGB, Feburary 1980 1/2
  - Student Teachers at CBGB, Feburary 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0064)
    Alternate title: Student Teachers at CBGB, Feburary 1980 2/2
  - Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0067)
    Alternate title: Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 1/3
  - Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0068)
    Alternate title: Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 2/3
  - Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0069)
    Alternate title: Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 3/3
  - Heartbreakers, John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0040)
    Alternate title: Heartbreakers, John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 1/4
  - Joe King Carrasco at CBGB, March 1980 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0070)
    Alternate title: Joe King Carrasco at CBGB, March 1980 1/2
  - Joe King Carrasco at CBGB, March 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0071)
    Alternate title: Joe King Carrasco at CBGB, March 1980 2/2
  - John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0073)
    Alternate title: John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 2/4
  - John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0074)
    Alternate title: John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 3/4
  - John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0075)
    Alternate title: John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 4/4
  - Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0077)
    Duration: 19 minutes
    Alternate title: Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 2/5
  - Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0078)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 3/5
  - Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0079)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 4/5
  - Rock Against Ratings: WPIX Band, Nuggets, Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0076)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Ratings: WPIX Band, Nuggets, Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 1/5
  - Offs Go East at Mudd Club, April 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0125)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Mudd Club, April 1980 1/6
  - Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0080)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 2/6
  - Offs Go East at Ambience, April 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0083)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 5/6
  - Offs Go East at Ambience, April 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0084)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Ambience, April 1980 6/6
  - Offs Go East at Rat Club, April 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0081)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 3/6
  - Offs Go East at Rat Club, April 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0082)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 4/6
  - Go-Go's at Danceteria, May 1980 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0130)
  - Max Blagg at Danceteria, May 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0092)
    Access DVD available.
  - Max Blagg at Danceteria, May 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0093)
    Duration: 13 minutes
  - Rock Against Racism: Heat, Cigaretz, Bad Brains at Central Park, May 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0088)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Stilettos, Casualties, Senders at Central Park, May 1980 3/5
  - Rock Against Racism: Lenny Kaye Band, Heat at Irving Plaza, May 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0085)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Lenny Kaye Band, Heat at Irving Plaza, May 1980 5/5
  - Rock Against Racism: Mass Appeal, Jitters at Central Park, May 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0086)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Mass Appeal, Jitters at Central Park, May 1980 1/5
  - Rock Against Racism: Senders at Central Park, May 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0090)
  - Rock Against Racism: Stilettos, Casualties, Senders at Central Park, May 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0087)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Stilettos, Casualties, Senders at Central Park, May 1980 2/5
  - Rock Against Racism: Terrorists, Panic Squad, Stilettos at Central Park, May 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0089)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Stilettos, Casualties, Senders at Central Park, May 1980 4/5
  - Raybeats at Danceteria, June 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0094)
  - Suburbs at Danceteria, June 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0128)
  - Suburbs at Danceteria, June 1980 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0129)
    Duration: 49 minutes
  - Ballistic Kisses at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0108)
    Duration: 41 minutes
  - Buzz and the Flyers at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0110)
    Duration: 37 minutes
  - DNA at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0131)
    Duration: 27 minutes
  - Feelies at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0102)
  - Human Sexual Response at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0091)
  - Kid Creole & the Coconuts at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0114)
  - Outsets at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0103)
    Duration: 52 minutes
  - Suicide at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0112)
  - Suicide at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0100)
    Duration: 36 minutes
  - Sun Ra at Danceteria, July 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0104)
  - Bush Tetras at Danceteria, August 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0122)
  - Pylon at Danceteria, August 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0097)
    Duration: 43 minutes
  - Strange Party at Danceteria, August 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0096)
  - Ballistic Kisses at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0099)
  - Joe King Carrasco at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0111)
    Alternate title: Joe King Carrasco at Danceteria, September 1980 2/2
  - Joe King Carrasco at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0072)
    Duration: 00:31:23
  - Offs at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0124)
    Alternate title: Offs at Danceteria, September 1980 1/2
  - Offs at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0113)
    Alternate title: Offs at Danceteria, September 1980 2/2
  - Plastics at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0109)
  - Pylon at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0098)
  - Raybeats at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0095)
  - Revelons at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0115)
    Alternate title: Revelons at Danceteria, September 1980 1/2
  - Revelons, Max Blagg at Danceteria, September 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0116)
    Alternate title: Revelons, Max Blagg at Danceteria, September 1980 2/2
  - Snow Storm at Lower East Side, 1977 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0144)
  - Rocket from the Tomb at Knitting Factory, June 2003 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0118)
    Original format: Betacam
  - Rocket from the Tomb at Knitting Factory, June 2003 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0117)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0143)
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
    Tape too phyically deteriorated to preserve.
  - Erasers at CBGB, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0137)
    Alternate Title: Erasers at CBGB 1/3
  - Erasers at CBGB, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0138)
    Alternate Title: Erasers at CBGB 2/3
  - Erasers at CBGB, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0139)
    Alternate Title: Erasers at CBGB 3/3
  - Erasers Edit at CBGB, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0140)
  - The Greying [Greening] of Central Park at Central Park, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0145)
  - "Hell in Paradise": Contortions & Stimulators at Paradise Garage, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0135)
    Audio intermittant and distorted throughout; no audio from 18 minutes 30 seconds to 24 minutes.
  - "Hell in Paradise": Richard Hell at Paradise Garage, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0132)
  - "Hell in Paradise": Richard Hell at Paradise Garage, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0133)
    Duration: 28 minutes
  - "Hell in Paradise": Senders at Paradise Garage, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0136)
  - "Hell in Paradise": Teenage Jesus and the Jerks at Paradise Garage, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0134)
    Duration: 9 minutes
    Audio intermittant and distorted throughout.
  - Son at CBGB, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0142)
  - Startoons at CBGB, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0141)
  - Three Nights on a Revolving Stage, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0147)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0151)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0152)
  - Bicentennial Time Campsules at Philadelphia, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0153)
    Original fDVD access copy available.ormat: 1/2" open reel
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0150)
  - [Blank Tape], undated (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0149)